Yes, it has begun. This is a special edition of the Nighttime and Idol Dialogue Series.
So, let me introduce the first group of idols who will appear on the stage this time.
Here are the first two. Please come in!
Are you ready to be dyed in Ruri's colors?
Yes!
Thank you very much. I'm Ruri Shiraishi, a first-year high school student from Shizuoka Prefecture,
Yes, I'm Ruri Shiraishi, a first-year high school student from Shizuoka Prefecture.
Butterfly, butterfly, butterfly, stop at Nanaha!
We will research the performance that will catch your eyes.
I am Nanaha Aoyama, a 14-year-old junior high school student.
Please call me Nanachan.
Please call me Nanae-chan, even if you are looking at me through the screen here.
Se-no!
Nana-chan!
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. That's all.
So, we have Ruri Shiraishi and Naho Aoyama from Ptaplat People Relay.
Please give them my best regards.
Thank you very much.
And one more pair. One more year. This time, we have a senior here to talk to you.
Please!
Hello.
Please.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Polycurumi.
Isn't that a little strange? What is okarumi? It's a little strange.
What's funny?
She's so senior.
Like a great actress.
She's a great actress.
It was good, wasn't it?
She was really good.
She's a kind junior.I am a kind junior.
My name is Kurumi Hori.
Pleased to meet you.
Please do.
Nice to meet you. Nice to meet you.
It's nice to meet you.
I've met you before, Ikuha-chan,
It's been a while.
It's nice to meet you too, Rina.
This time, right?
I'd like to learn how to survive in the entertainment industry as an idol talent from Horii-senpai,
I'd like to learn from Mr. Horii about how to survive in the entertainment industry as an idol talent.
Well, I'm sorry, I'm...
I'm so happy.
I'm so happy!
I'd love to learn a lot from you.
I'll only teach you the weirdest things today.
Ha-ha-ha.
I see.
Well, what we were doing was...
When we do festivals and events...
It's hard for the audience to see from far away.
It's hard for them to see.
So, as a last resort, we wrote on a big panel
We would write "search for takoyaki rainbow" on a large panel and hold it up for a long time.
Also, if we did idol events...
Our songs are often in Kansai dialect,
Our songs are very different from those of other groups,
So we put so many of them in that our fans would listen to them.
We put so many songs in that our fans would listen to them.
We also did a lot of live shows where we served Kansai food all the time.
I see. We also had live shows where we served Kansai food all over the place.
I see.
So it would be better for us to show our charm as Stapler students.
I definitely think that would be better.
If there were many other idols,If there are many other idols,
I was wondering if there were many other idols, and if there were many other idols, what would be the difference between the STAPLA research students and the other idols?
There are so many of us,
Each one of them has a strong individuality.
So each one of us has different strengths,
I would probably face a lot of hurdles no matter what they ask me to do,
It's great.
I am sure that one of us will be able to do whatever is asked of us.
That's amazing. What's that?
I don't know.
Really? No one can do it. On the contrary.
Really?
Yes, and the youngest is in the first grade.
Wow! So young!
Since they are small, I thought I could show them how fresh they are and how energetic they are.
Wow, a first grader! That's amazing!
Nakai-iro
Are you doing Nakai Iro? We're doing Nakai Iro, and we get along so well.
We get along so well in the dressing room that it's noisy.
The members send me pictures of their funny faces on LINE.
That's a good friendship.
That's good friendship.
I feel relieved.
Q. What are your future goals? Oh, but this is something that a fan told me right after the group was formed.
Wow!
How to give lessons
That's great!
He sent me a letter with a lot of instructions on how to do it.
I'm just going to blurt out what was written in the letter...
I have a venue and I want to tell everyone about it, but
I want to tell everyone, but I can't look them in the eye
I'm going to start by making eye contact with each and every one of you.
Even if you say thank you to everybody, you look at somebody else, and so on,
So I'd start by making eye contact with everyone,
It's okay if you can't make eye contact with everyone, he said, so just slowly make eye contact with each person one by one.He told me that it was okay if I couldn't make eye contact with everyone, but that I should slowly make eye contact with each person one by one.
That's what I was told.
I will try it.
I think it's really good. I'm sure I'll be able to see everyone one by one.
I was under the impression that I should try to make eye contact with each person for about 3 seconds? I think it's really good.
Isn't that right?
That's what I thought.
And then...
But...
When we're playing in a venue that's quite deep...
I try to take a video afterwards.
I try to take video afterwards, but there are times when I think I'm doing something big, but the power is really flying downwards,
From the back, it looks like I'm dancing too small,
So I was conscious of it, and it looked a little weird,
So I was consciously doing it a little weirdly.
I wanted to look over there, but I would aim a little higher.
I think this way, the power will reach to the back of the stage.
Thank you very much.
Okay, let's do it like this.
Bend over a little.
I can see your line of sight really well.
I can kill two birds with one stone.
It looks so much bigger. That way, you're moving. Isn't that good? Now.
Wasn't that a little too teacher-like?
Yes, it does.
Q. Show us the stage movement.
A. Yes, that's good. I want to see it.
Can I see it here?
You can watch it here, and you can watch it from this side.
Let's see it from this side.
Q. Can I see the stage movement? I'd like you to watch from this side, and I'll watch from this side.
Three, two, one, go ahead.
Oh, cute.
Cute.
I was going to give you a stern look, but I just laughed like a normal person.
What's the score now?What is your current score?
Now that's a perfect score of 150.
Yay!
Super amateur!
Now please 321 to Mr. Aoyama's effective race during the live.
Thank you.
Cute!
That's a perfect score of 350.
Wow!
How did you get a perfect score?
Well, she was out of focus, so that was cute, too.
I need to be more camera conscious.
The out-of-focus part was cute, too.
Thank you very much.
That's nice.
They are both so cute.
I'm about to draw the second volume of this, and I should do it towards different people and 1 eye is right on, right?
Yes. Because if the customer is looking at the bar, I can't remember everyone and everything,
If they think they see me, they will definitely remember me,
So I hope I can win the heart of each and every one of them.
I will go to the next show as soon as possible.
All right!
Is there anything you pay attention to?
Yes. Yes, I do. I think the thing that makes my fans happiest is when they hear me say their names.
When I meet someone for the first time, I ask them what their name is in a short time.
I write it down and memorize it.
Wow! That's a lot of effort!
Is that something you can remember?
Yes, I can. I'll always write down "Nanny Nanny".
Of course, the story is important too, but you have to remember "Nanny Nanny" in the other head.
Wow! That's great craftsmanship.
I'm so happy!
How are you doing? How about you, Rinori?
I haven't done many benefit events or storytelling sessions, but I try to communicate with them.
I try to be communicative and conversational, and I ask them how their hair is today.I try to have a conversation so that we can communicate, and I try to ask her how her hair is today.
I also try to have a conversation about what I ate.
Do you talk to each other?
You're both doing a great job.
I don't remember me being like that.
It's coming to an end.
But I've been careful.
I'm trying to keep the conversation going.
I'm trying to remember names.
But when I first started, I was so full of it.
All I could do was talk at the moment.
Hold her tight.
Squeeze, squeeze, squeeze
I won't let go until the very last minute.
Aah!
Was it?
That's so nice.
I don't even know what I'm saying anymore.
That's all I've been paying attention to.
I see.
But I think it works really well.
Oh, wow.
I'll do it, I'll do it.
Okay, I'll do it.
Use it anytime.
Anytime.
Well, I have an assignment for the staff and research students, which is to make the MC look natural,
There is no challenge.
I'm talking about ourselves.
How can we MC naturally?
How do you do it now?
Do you have a script?
Yes, I do. We have a solid script,
Then we try to expand the topics for free talk,
It doesn't go very well.It doesn't work very well.
It's difficult, isn't it?
But when we make a firm decision, everyone acts as if we have made a firm decision,
But on the other hand, when we do free talk, we talk for an hour and a half.
We once talked for an hour and a half during an encore because everyone was too excited,
At the very first show.
At that time, I was really scolded,
So I said, "It's not good if we just do free talk,
So I decided on a title for the talk at the beginning,
We would have one free talk in the dressing room.
We would have one free talk in the dressing room,
I would talk once in the dressing room and get a good feeling for the flow of the conversation,
We would talk once in the dressing room, and then we would decide on the flow of the talk and what we were going to say because it was interesting,
In the beginning, we were like, "Why are you doing this?
We were like, "Why not? I thought it was decided that way,
But in the end, it was the easiest way to do it.
Thank you.
I'll try to speak freely.
That's true.
Let's try it backstage.
Let's do it.
I think it will be much easier.
If it's completely free, then bye-bye bye-bye.
I'm sure you're right.
So, let's talk one more time,
I can do it already.
I can do that now.
Thank you very much.
Q. What are your future goals?
I get nervous easily,
I would like to know how to cope with nervousness.
I get nervous too.
I get nervous at events. I also get nervous at events. I get nervous easily.
Like events.
But I don't know.
If we were to do an event with our own guests...If we do an event with our own audience.
I think it's cute that they're even nervous.
Oh!
So instead of hiding it and being stiff.
I think it's cuter if you chew something or make a mistake.
I think it's totally cuter if you make a mistake.
I think it's totally cuter when they make mistakes,
I think that's the beauty of being raw.
If not, try your best to look like you are not nervous.
Are you hiding that you are not nervous?
I'm not nervous.
I'll do my best.
Thank you very much. Perhaps, while everyone in the staff writing system often goes to the live performances of other senior idols in STAFRA,
Speaking of Mr. Hori, among the Staffra members,
He is the only one who can call on Momota-san to call on him,
He is the only one who can call out to Momota-san among the other idols,
He also intertwined with other idols,
He has left his mark in many ways,
I have the image of him leaving his mark on other idols,
I have an image that you leave your mark when you go out to other places in Staffra, so what should I do to leave my mark when I go out to other places in Staffra?
Is there anything I can do?
I don't know.
I think it's important to try to do your best and then make a big mistake later on.
If I make a huge mistake afterwards, I'll think it's okay, so I'll start to wonder if I said too much or too little, and then I'll think it's okay.
I think it's better not to worry about it, and to just go on and on as if I've already eaten it all up.
It's better to go in with a gusto, like I've already eaten all the food.
I'll get angry at you for saying that.
I think it's better to be like that.
Thank you very much.
Gutsy.
I was curious about you because you are very interesting and I respect you a lot.
You're just the way you are. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.
But I was really too nervous at the beginning,
I couldn't speak at all in the presence of my seniors,
I thought it would be a good time to suddenly put in my stomach muscles,I was wondering if there would come a time when I would suddenly put in some abs,
Because there are times when you suddenly feel like I'm done with this,
I'll do my best to eat at that time.
Next time, we will talk about activities outside the idol world,
I would like to learn from Hori Tenka, alone,
So please look forward to it.
That's all for this time.
Now, please give your final greetings.
So far, we have been with
Hori Kurubi and
Rui Shiraishi and
Nanaha Aoyama.
See you tomorrow.
Bye bye!
Bye!